(Penny:)How long
has this been going on?
Four months.
(Sheldon:)She's not my girlfriend.
Are you telling me, for
the past four months
(Penny:)I have been asking you,
"What's new?"
(Penny:)and you never thought
to go with,
"Sheldon has a girlfriend"?
She's not my girlfriend.
Ah... d-d-d-d...
(Penny:)How did they meet?
(Howard:)Raj and I entered Sheldon's
information on a dating site,
(Howard:)and it spit out
Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Penny:)Oh, my God!
Sheldon and Amy.
(Howard:)Or, as we
call them, "Shamy."
(Howard:)Shamy.
(Penny(squeals):)I am so digging the Shamy.
(Penny:)All right,
everyone pay attention.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I have a friend
named Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Sheldon:)Yes, she is female.
(Sheldon:)Yes, we communicate
on a daily basis,
(Sheldon:)but no, she is not
my girlfriend.
(Penny:)Okay, well, what do
you communicate about?
(Sheldon:)Well, my work in physics,
her work in neurobiology,
(Sheldon:)and most recently,
the possibility
(Sheldon:)of our having a child together.
(Penny(spits out drink explosively. Howard types. Robot arm hands Penny a napkin):)Thank you.